znetindia.com 2013-03-28

# Privacy Policy | ZNetLive

This privacy statement describes how ZNet Technologies Pvt Ltd collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [http://www.znetlive.in](http://www.znetlive.in/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

ZNet Technologies Pvt Ltd has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at abuse@znetlive.in. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * If you are registering on behalf of your organization, your company’s name, mailing address, and other company information

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to

  * Respond to customer service & offer requests
  * Administer your account
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
You may choose to stop receiving our emails by logging into your account and updating your notification selections or you can contact us at [info@znetlive.in](mailto:info@znetlive.in). We enable you to create an account, and share information such as messages, offers, & requests with others.

**Refer A Friend**   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. If you provide us personal information about others (such as providing information about another individual to allow them access when creating a sub-account) we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. ZNet Technologies Pvt Ltd stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [info@znetlive.in](mailto:info@znetlive.in) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Information Sharing**  
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service (such as utilizing our ‘Live Chat’ feature). These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if ZNet Technologies Pvt Ltd is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

_**Cookies**_  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use persistent cookie to store user id and session cookie to store different master ids. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

we use persistent cookie to store user id and session cookie to store different master ids.

_**Tracking Technologies &Third Party Cookies**_  
The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers are not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

We use Google Analytics, a third-party tracking service, which uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about our visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics. Some of our business partners (e.g., Google Analytics) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by ZNet Technologies Pvt Ltd only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party.

_**Web beacons**_  
Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

_**Flash LSOs**_  
We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118>

_**Links to Other Web Sites  
**_Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of ZNet Technologies Pvt Ltd. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [info@znetlive.in](mailto:info@znetlive.in)

**Additional Policy Information**  
Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs & community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [info@znetlive.in](mailto:info@znetlive.in). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

You can link to our site using social networking services such as Facebook & Twitter. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your sign-in information, name and email address to link between the sites. Services like Facebook & Twitter give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at [info@znetlive.in](mailto:info@znetlive.in)

**Correcting, Deleting and Updating Your Personal Information**  
To review, delete and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, you may login to your account or contact us directly at [info@znetlive.in](mailto:info@znetlive.in)

**Data Retention**  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [email address]. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes  
**We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**  
You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:  
**ZNet Technologies Pvt Ltd**  
D-10/52, Chitrakoot, Vaishali Nagar  
Jaipur  
Rajasthan  
302021  
India   
91-141-4070666  
Email: [info@znetlive.in](mailto:info@znetlive.in)
